I
我
probably already familiar with the view life cycle map
可能已经熟悉视图生命周期图了
or create
或者创造
yay did
是的
are MT
是MT吗
update
更新
updated
or destroy
或者毁灭
and destroyed if you're not familiar with these positive video read the descriptions
如果你不熟悉这些正面的视频，就把它销毁
we got
我们有
some additional view to life cycle methods which were released in recent versions I want to make sure you're familiar with
在最近的版本中发布的一些生命周期方法的附加视图，我想确保您熟悉这些方法
vs activated
vs激活
this is used when you have dynamic components
当您有动态组件时使用此选项
keep alive
活下去
the component inside keep alive as toggled on
内部组件保持激活状态
and there is deactivated
还有一个是无效的
when the component inside keep alive is
当keep alive内部的组件
both
二者都
off
远离的
Erik captured
埃里克被捕了
this is called
这叫做
air from any descendant component
来自任何后代的空气
is captured
被捕获
want to learn more about how these work check out the documentation
想了解更多关于这些工作原理的信息请查看文档
let's now dive into
现在让我们深入了解
changes with you
随您更改
I
我
before destroy life cycle method
销毁前生命周期法
also be written as
也写为
for on mount
用于装载
should work
应该行得通
also destroyed
也被摧毁了
I also use
我也用
on mounted
安装
they should both work with you three and when I asked avenue why this change
他们应该和你们三个一起工作当我问avenue为什么要改变
it's pretty much because
这在很大程度上是因为
it's a better naming convention
这是一个更好的命名约定
mount the component
安装部件
and be on mount components
安装组件
simply add
只需添加
on to the call back name
回叫的名字
inside the setup method
设置方法内部
here's what that might look like for before MT
这是MT之前可能会出现的情况
on mounted we need to import them
我们需要进口
then we can simply use them sending in anonymous functions inside of our setup method
然后我们可以简单地使用它们在setup方法内部发送匿名函数
list of all the different life cycle methods we can use inside the setup method
我们可以在设置方法内部使用的所有不同生命周期方法的列表
if you're being observant
如果你有观察力
you might notice that two are missing
你可能注意到有两个不见了
create and created are not needed when we're using the composition a p I and we have that set up method
create和created在使用compositionapi时是不需要的，我们有设置方法
this is because before create
这是因为在创建之前
called right before set up
设置前打过电话
and then created is called
然后被称为
right after setup
安装后马上
code that would normally be put inside of these hooks
通常放在这些钩子中的代码
now being placed inside of our setup method
现在被放置在我们的设置方法内部
example here would be AP calls
这里的例子是AP电话
we put those inside of before create or created and instead
我们把它们放在创造或创造之前
you can call them from our set at method
你可以从我们的set at方法调用它们
are two new view three life cycle methods the first of which is on rendered tract
两个新的视图三个生命周期方法，其中第一个是在渲染域上
this is called when a reactive dependency is first being accessed in the render function during render
当在呈现期间第一次在render函数中访问反应性依赖项时，将调用此函数
meaning this dependency will now be
意味着这种依赖现在
I
我
rangers
游骑兵
hook can be helpful when we want to see which dependencies are being tracked
当我们想查看正在跟踪哪些依赖项时，钩子很有用
debugging purposes
调试目的
also there's on rendered trigger
也有一个渲染触发器
this is called when a new render is triggered allowing you to inspect which dependency triggered a component to re render
当触发新渲染时，将调用此选项，允许您检查哪个依赖项触发了要重新渲染的组件
as you can imagine this is going to make the bugging a lot easier
你可以想象这会让窃听变得容易得多
we need to figure out which dependencies
我们需要找出哪些依赖关系
are being tracked
正在被跟踪
in which dependencies are triggering our component to re render
其中依赖关系将触发组件重新呈现
also can be good when we're doing performance optimism
当我们表现乐观的时候也会很好
really excited to see what sort of optimization tools can be created
很高兴看到可以创建什么样的优化工具
entering around these hooks
进入这些钩子周围